5dollarmoneybomb.com 2012-04-15

# Privacy Policy

5DollarMoneyBomb.com ("5DollarMoneyBomb" or "we") respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy documents our adherence to the highest industry standards for the protection of your personal information. By visiting this web site or using any of the services offered on the Site, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 15, 2011, applies to information collected through the Site and covers the following areas:

1\. Information Collection and Use

5DollarMoneyBomb collects information on the Site at two different stages. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information (such as domain name or IP address) from all visitors to the Site. This type of information is never linked to any personally identifiable information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical reports about the use of the Site.

Second, we require the submission of certain personally identifiable information when you use the services available on the Site. For example, your use of your username and password allows us to identify you as a subscriber of 5DollarMoneyBomb.com.

2\. Personal Information of Children Under 13

5DollarMoneyBomb complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") and the FTC's rule interpreting COPPA (16 CFR § 512). This Site is not directed to children and we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age through this Site.

3\. Use of Your Personal Information

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, 5DollarMoneyBomb does not sell, rent, or share user information to or with any third party not affiliated with or owned by 5DollarMoneyBomb, except service providers who may assist 5DollarMoneyBomb in areas such as data storage. 5DollarMoneyBomb will never give or sell your personal information to be used for the purposes of sending you unsolicited commercial offers (such as SPAM) from any third party. 

We may use your personal information to send you unsolicited commercial offers related to 5DollarMoneyBomb.com or other income opportunities, or to contact you for purposes other than marketing, as for example regarding the status of the Site, your account or other matters related to your role as a subscriber and affiliate of Silver2Up.com. We may contact you using any method available including email, text messaging, or any other method current existing or later invented, and you agree to incur any related expenses related to receiving these messages. You may not opt-out of these kinds of communications.

4\. Use of Aggregate Information

We store information that we collect through log files to create a profile of our users. Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. A profile is stored information detailing how individual users use the Site. It is used solely for internal purposes, to help us improve the experience of our users. We do not share your profile with any third parties.

5\. Disclosure of Personal Information

We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) protect and defend our rights, or (c) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others.

You understand and agree your personal information will be made publicly available in the following circumstances:

  * Your name and phone number will be displayed on your marketing website so others may contact you. 

  * Your name, mailing address, phone number and NetSpend account number will be displayed to new subscribers so they may pay you.

6\. Business Transfers

In the event 5DollarMoneyBomb goes through a business transition or a transfer, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, or in the unlikely event that 5DollarMoneyBomb goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, our user's personal information may be part of the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of 5DollarMoneyBomb or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

7\. Links

The Site contains links to other web sites. 5DollarMoneyBomb is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Site.

8\. Security

5DollarMoneyBomb takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your information. However, given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information.

We also make an effort to protect your information off-line. All of our user's information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.

When registering for access to a secure area of the Site, we will ask you to select a username and password. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, remember to log out of the registered site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence when accessing your computer.

9\. Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may make changes through the "My Profile" tab within your back office.

10\. Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will prominently post a notice on the main control panel of your back office to alert you of the change. If the Privacy Policy changes materially so that your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you by e-mail to give you a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this different manner. However, you are responsible for ensuring we have a current working e-mail address for you. If the e-mail address you have given us is incorrect or no longer operable, we will have no further obligation to notify you apart from posting the notice on our Site. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on the main page notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

11\. Contact Information

For further information about this site, please [contact us](http://www.silver1up.info/contact_us.htm)
